<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>I014 Magazine</title>
    <link href="https://blog.intron014.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://blog.intron014.com" />
    <updated>2022-01-28T21:26:14+01:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Intron014</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://blog.intron014.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Close Encounters of the Third Kind</title>
        <author>
            <name>Intron014</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://blog.intron014.com/close-encounters-of-the-third-kind/"/>
        <id>https://blog.intron014.com/close-encounters-of-the-third-kind/</id>
            <category term="iPad"/>
            <category term="Apple"/>

        <updated>2022-01-28T21:26:14+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://blog.intron014.com/media/posts/5/og__544tqbfss1ua_image.png" alt="Apple" />
                     Well... I finally gave into the Apple ecosystem after trying countless (as a matter of fact, 5) android tablets, none of which, were up for my school note-taking life. Nevertheless, when Apple announced in their Apple Event the 9th Generation of the iPad I&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://blog.intron014.com/media/posts/5/og__544tqbfss1ua_image.png" alt="Apple" />
                
  <p>
    Well... I finally gave into the Apple ecosystem after trying countless (as a matter of fact, 5) android tablets, none of which, were up for my school note-taking life. Nevertheless, when Apple announced in their Apple Event the 9th Generation of the iPad I thought to myself, "Why not?" And got it with a Logitech Crayon because... Honestly, I know that it has way less functionality than the Apple Pencil, but the shape... ANYWAYS! We're getting off track. Where were we... Oh yeah! The iPad.
  </p>

  <div  class="gallery-wrapper gallery-wrapper--center">
    <div class="gallery" data-columns="3">
      <figure class="gallery__item">
      <a href="https://blog.intron014.com/media/posts/5/gallery/ipad-202109-gallery-1.jpg" data-size="2822x2400">
        <img loading="lazy" src="https://blog.intron014.com/media/posts/5/gallery/ipad-202109-gallery-1-thumbnail.jpg" height="612" width="720" alt="" />
      </a>
      
    </figure><figure class="gallery__item">
      <a href="https://blog.intron014.com/media/posts/5/gallery/ipad-202109-gallery-2.jpg" data-size="2822x2400">
        <img loading="lazy" src="https://blog.intron014.com/media/posts/5/gallery/ipad-202109-gallery-2-thumbnail.jpg" height="612" width="720" alt="" />
      </a>
      
    </figure><figure class="gallery__item">
      <a href="https://blog.intron014.com/media/posts/5/gallery/ipad-202109-gallery-4.jpg" data-size="2824x2400">
        <img loading="lazy" src="https://blog.intron014.com/media/posts/5/gallery/ipad-202109-gallery-4-thumbnail.jpg" height="612" width="720" alt="" />
      </a>
      
    </figure><figure class="gallery__item">
      <a href="https://blog.intron014.com/media/posts/5/gallery/ipad-202109-gallery-3_GEO_US.jpg" data-size="4056x2400">
        <img loading="lazy" src="https://blog.intron014.com/media/posts/5/gallery/ipad-202109-gallery-3_GEO_US-thumbnail.jpg" height="426" width="720" alt="" />
      </a>
      
    </figure><figure class="gallery__item">
      <a href="https://blog.intron014.com/media/posts/5/gallery/ipad-202109-gallery-5.jpg" data-size="4056x2400">
        <img loading="lazy" src="https://blog.intron014.com/media/posts/5/gallery/ipad-202109-gallery-5-thumbnail.jpg" height="426" width="720" alt="" />
      </a>
      
    </figure>
    </div>
  </div>

  <p>
    From the moment I booted iPadOS 15 I fell in love with the simple yet incredibly powerful OS (And to be completely honest, I was blown away by the multitasking). To be clear, my goal buying the iPad was to have a device that I could take to school, get rid of my physical notebooks and books, and just... Carry it! Practically no weight at all.
  </p>

  <p>
    As of writing this post, I've been using the iPad for a month and a bit. I've been using GoodNotes for my notetaking, as well as Quick Notes for when I have to jot something on the go (Perfect for when the teacher starts saying what's gonna be in the exam and you have nothing open). You might be wondering what has been of my previous notes on the physical notebooks, so the answer is... I scanned them all! I might not conserve the OCR but to be honest, I didn't have that either before.
  </p>

    <figure class="post__image post__image--center">
      <img loading="lazy" src="https://blog.intron014.com/media/posts/5/Imagen-PNG_ipad_spacegrey_landscape.png" sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://blog.intron014.com/media/posts/5/responsive/Imagen-PNG_ipad_spacegrey_landscape-xs.png 300w ,https://blog.intron014.com/media/posts/5/responsive/Imagen-PNG_ipad_spacegrey_landscape-sm.png 480w ,https://blog.intron014.com/media/posts/5/responsive/Imagen-PNG_ipad_spacegrey_landscape-md.png 768w ,https://blog.intron014.com/media/posts/5/responsive/Imagen-PNG_ipad_spacegrey_landscape-lg.png 1024w ,https://blog.intron014.com/media/posts/5/responsive/Imagen-PNG_ipad_spacegrey_landscape-xl.png 1360w ,https://blog.intron014.com/media/posts/5/responsive/Imagen-PNG_ipad_spacegrey_landscape-2xl.png 1600w"  height="1920" width="2710" alt="" />
      
    </figure>

  <p>
    On another note, shortcuts has been of great help! As you can see by the screenshot above, I have a very handy dandy Shortcut to add a new exam to my calendar following my usual naming scheme, perfection! (Also starring... Widgetsmith and Apollo!)
  </p>

  <p>
    So yeah, in conclussion... This iPad is really (for what I've been able to tell for now) a great device!
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Orange</title>
        <author>
            <name>Intron014</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://blog.intron014.com/the-orange/"/>
        <id>https://blog.intron014.com/the-orange/</id>
            <category term="Poem"/>
            <category term="Oranges"/>

        <updated>2022-01-25T08:54:11+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://blog.intron014.com/media/posts/4/1652387-1.jpg" alt="Oranges, lots of slices" />
                     The other day in English class, we read a poem. A really interesting poem at that. It is called The Orange (Look! Just loke this entry's title! How surprising), and this poem is... well, it makes you think about how even the smallest things&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://blog.intron014.com/media/posts/4/1652387-1.jpg" alt="Oranges, lots of slices" />
                
  <p>
    The other day in English class, we read a poem. A really interesting poem at that.<br>It is called The Orange (Look! Just loke this entry's title! How surprising), and this poem is... well, it makes you think about how even the smallest things in life can make you happy. It makes me feel like we shouldn’t take everything seriously and we should just enjoy life, take a walk, breathe... Just getting away from the busy life that is ours.&nbsp;<br><br>This poem was written (or at least published) in 1993, so it's as we say now.. Pre-COVID. Life as it is, and reading this made me realize that we used to life a quieter and more relaxed life than we do as of right now. Anyways, here's the poem, by Wendy Cope:<br>
  </p>

    <figure class="blockquote">
      <blockquote>The Orange<br><br>At lunchtime I bought a huge orange—<br>The size of it made us all laugh.<br>I peeled it and shared it with Robert and Dave—<br>They got quarters and I had a half.<br><br>And that orange, it made me so happy,<br>As ordinary things often do<br>Just lately. The shopping. A walk in the park.<br>This is peace and contentment. It’s new.<br><br>The rest of the day was quite easy.<br>I did all the jobs on my list<br>And enjoyed them and had some time over.<br>I love you. I’m glad I exist.<br></blockquote>
      <figcaption>Wendy Cope</figcaption>
    </figure>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Hello, and welcome!</title>
        <author>
            <name>Intron014</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://blog.intron014.com/hello-and-welcome/"/>
        <id>https://blog.intron014.com/hello-and-welcome/</id>
            <category term="Welcome!"/>

        <updated>2022-01-23T12:10:27+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://blog.intron014.com/media/posts/3/TeslaIntron_3_Ped.png" alt="Intron Driving a Red Tesla Model 3" />
                     Hello, and welcome to my blog! As what may have brought you here, I do not know, but I sincerely hope that you stay to follow on my... how to say it... my silly little adventures trying to figure out everything to be honest&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://blog.intron014.com/media/posts/3/TeslaIntron_3_Ped.png" alt="Intron Driving a Red Tesla Model 3" />
                
  <p>
    Hello, and welcome to my blog! As what may have brought you here, I do not know, but I sincerely hope that you stay to follow on my... how to say it... my silly little adventures trying to figure out everything to be honest (maybe I'll even honor this page's name and I'll do weekly releases!). Anyways... If you'd like to get notifications whenever I post anything here, I have a <a href="https://l.intron014.com/nr5Z" target="_blank">Telegram channel</a>&nbsp;(&lt;--- click there :D) for you!&nbsp;
  </p>

  <p>
    Thanks for checking this out! Cya in the next issue!<br>- Intron014.<br>
  </p>

  <p>
    
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
